<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Aspect</title><link>https://cloudaspect.app/</link><description>Recent content on Aspect</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 22:10:26 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://cloudaspect.app/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Configuration</title><link>https://cloudaspect.app/docs/aws/configuration/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 22:10:26 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://cloudaspect.app/docs/aws/configuration/</guid><description>Coming Soon!
Docker:
docker run --rm -it -v $HOME/.aws:/root/.aws:ro im5tu/aspect:latest</description></item><item><title>Configuration</title><link>https://cloudaspect.app/docs/azure/configuration/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 22:10:26 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://cloudaspect.app/docs/azure/configuration/</guid><description>Coming Soon!</description></item><item><title>Installation</title><link>https://cloudaspect.app/docs/getting-started/installation/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 22:10:26 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://cloudaspect.app/docs/getting-started/installation/</guid><description>The fastest way to get started with Aspect is to use the Docker image from Docker Hub:
docker pull im5tu/aspect Once pulled, you can run the docker image like so:
docker run -it --rm im5tu/aspect This will start a new command line with the aspect command available so you can then run one of the available commands straight away. Depending which cloud resource you intend to use, you may also need to mount credential folders.</description></item><item><title>AwsAccount</title><link>https://cloudaspect.app/docs/aws/resources/awsaccount/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cloudaspect.app/docs/aws/resources/awsaccount/</guid><description>The AWS account resource describes the details of the account that a specified resource belongs to.
Note: You will not be able to write a policy directly against this type.
Properties Name Description Type Id The account identifier specific to the cloud provider AwsAccountIdentifier Type The type of the account, eg: AWS/Azure/GCP String Policy Template This template will give you a quick head start on generating a policy for an AwsAccount:</description></item><item><title>AzureAccount</title><link>https://cloudaspect.app/docs/azure/resources/azureaccount/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cloudaspect.app/docs/azure/resources/azureaccount/</guid><description>Note: You will not be able to write a policy directly against this type.
Properties Name Description Type Id The account identifier specific to the cloud provider AzureAccountIdentifier Type The type of the account, eg: AWS/Azure/GCP String Policy Template This template will give you a quick head start on generating a policy for an AzureAccount:
resource &amp;quot;AzureAccount&amp;quot; validate { } Nested Types AzureAccountIdentifier Properties Name Description Type</description></item><item><title>Developing Locally</title><link>https://cloudaspect.app/docs/contributing/local-development/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cloudaspect.app/docs/contributing/local-development/</guid><description>If you wish to modify an aspect of Aspect, you&amp;rsquo;ll need the source code. Clone via one of the following methods:
Clone using SSH git clone --recurse-submodules git@github.com:Im5tu/aspect.git Clone using Github CLI gh repo clone Im5tu/aspect Clone using HTTPS git clone --recurse-submodules https://github.com/Im5tu/aspect.git Building &amp;amp; Running tests In order to build a development build, execute the following command:
dotnet build In order to run the unit tests, execute:
dotnet test The solution is designed to take care of any dependencies that are required so that contributors have the best experience in their local development environments.</description></item><item><title>Policy Syntax</title><link>https://cloudaspect.app/docs/getting-started/policy-syntax/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 22:10:26 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://cloudaspect.app/docs/getting-started/policy-syntax/</guid><description>Coming soon!!</description></item><item><title>aspect inspect</title><link>https://cloudaspect.app/docs/cli-commands/aspect-inspect/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cloudaspect.app/docs/cli-commands/aspect-inspect/</guid><description>A REPL instance to execute commands against cloud resources for verification_
aspect inspect &amp;lt;path&amp;gt; Arguments Option Position Description Default Required? Options Option Alias Description Default</description></item><item><title>AwsSecurityGroup</title><link>https://cloudaspect.app/docs/aws/resources/awssecuritygroup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cloudaspect.app/docs/aws/resources/awssecuritygroup/</guid><description>A security group acts as a virtual firewall for your instance to control inbound and outbound traffic. A security group specifies the actions that are allowed, not the actions that are blocked.
Properties Name Description Type Account The account that is associated with the resource. AwsAccount Arn The Amazon Resource Names (ARN) uniquely identifying an AWS resource. String Description A friendly description of what the security group allows.</description></item><item><title>Compiler Structure</title><link>https://cloudaspect.app/docs/contributing/compiler/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cloudaspect.app/docs/contributing/compiler/</guid><description>Lexer TBC!
Parser TBC!
Lightweight Code Gen TBC!</description></item><item><title>Policy Suite Syntax</title><link>https://cloudaspect.app/docs/getting-started/policy-suite-syntax/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 22:10:26 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://cloudaspect.app/docs/getting-started/policy-suite-syntax/</guid><description>Coming soon!!</description></item><item><title>Pull Requests</title><link>https://cloudaspect.app/docs/contributing/pull-requests/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cloudaspect.app/docs/contributing/pull-requests/</guid><description>Coming soon!!</description></item><item><title>Builtin Functions</title><link>https://cloudaspect.app/docs/getting-started/builtin-functions/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 22:10:26 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://cloudaspect.app/docs/getting-started/builtin-functions/</guid><description>When building your policies, you may which to perform certain operations like seeing whether or not a string contains a specific value. Aspect provides you with a set of built in functions to help you.
All of the functions follow this format:
functionName(input.&amp;lt;property&amp;gt;, &amp;lt;arg1&amp;gt; [, arg2..]) The first argument to each function must be an accessor to a property on the input. This is followed by the function arguments specified in one of the functions below.</description></item><item><title>aspect policy init</title><link>https://cloudaspect.app/docs/cli-commands/aspect-policy-init/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cloudaspect.app/docs/cli-commands/aspect-policy-init/</guid><description>Create a new policy at the specified location:
aspect policy init &amp;lt;filename&amp;gt; Arguments Option Position Description Default Required? filname 0 The filename where the template policy will be created true</description></item><item><title>aspect policy list</title><link>https://cloudaspect.app/docs/cli-commands/aspect-policy-list/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cloudaspect.app/docs/cli-commands/aspect-policy-list/</guid><description>List all of the policies and their resource types within the specified directory. By default, only the current directory is searched, but recursion is available.
aspect policy list &amp;lt;directory&amp;gt; Arguments Option Position Description Default Required? directory 0 The filename or directory to validate Current directory true Options Option Alias Description Default &amp;ndash;recursive -r Whether or not to recurse through child directories false</description></item><item><title>aspect policy validate</title><link>https://cloudaspect.app/docs/cli-commands/aspect-policy-validate/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cloudaspect.app/docs/cli-commands/aspect-policy-validate/</guid><description>Validate a specific file or directory to ensure that the policy is valid before running it using aspect run. If specifying a directory, the options listed below will also be available.
aspect policy validate &amp;lt;path&amp;gt; [-r|--recursive] [--failed-only] Arguments Option Position Description Default Required? path 0 The filename or directory to validate Current directory true Options Option Alias Description Default &amp;ndash;recursive -r Whether or not to recurse through child directories false &amp;ndash;failed-only Displays only invalid policies.</description></item><item><title>aspect resources</title><link>https://cloudaspect.app/docs/cli-commands/aspect-resources/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cloudaspect.app/docs/cli-commands/aspect-resources/</guid><description>aspect resources &amp;lt;provider&amp;gt; Arguments Option Position Description Default Required? path 0 The filename or directory to validate Current directory true Options Option Alias Description Default</description></item><item><title>aspect run</title><link>https://cloudaspect.app/docs/cli-commands/aspect-run/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cloudaspect.app/docs/cli-commands/aspect-run/</guid><description>aspect run &amp;lt;path&amp;gt; Arguments Option Position Description Default Required? path 0 The filename or directory to validate Current directory true Options Option Alias Description Default</description></item><item><title>aspect watch</title><link>https://cloudaspect.app/docs/cli-commands/aspect-watch/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cloudaspect.app/docs/cli-commands/aspect-watch/</guid><description>Watch a specific directory for changes and validate them as the files change.
aspect watch &amp;lt;directory&amp;gt; Arguments Option Position Description Default Required? directory 0 The directory to watch for changes Current directory true Options Option Alias Description Default &amp;ndash;delay -r The period of time in milliseconds that needs to elapse between changes to a file.</description></item><item><title>Code of Conduct</title><link>https://cloudaspect.app/docs/contributing/code-of-conduct/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cloudaspect.app/docs/contributing/code-of-conduct/</guid><description>Our Pledge We as members, contributors, and leaders pledge to make participation in our community a harassment-free experience for everyone, regardless of age, body size, visible or invisible disability, ethnicity, sex characteristics, gender identity and expression, level of experience, education, socio-economic status, nationality, personal appearance, race, caste, color, religion, or sexual identity and orientation.
We pledge to act and interact in ways that contribute to an open, welcoming, diverse, inclusive, and healthy community.</description></item></channel></rss>