<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Resources on Aspect</title><link>https://cloudaspect.app/docs/aws/resources/</link><description>Recent content in Resources on Aspect</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://cloudaspect.app/docs/aws/resources/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>AwsAccount</title><link>https://cloudaspect.app/docs/aws/resources/awsaccount/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cloudaspect.app/docs/aws/resources/awsaccount/</guid><description>The AWS account resource describes the details of the account that a specified resource belongs to.
Note: You will not be able to write a policy directly against this type. Properties Name Description Type Id The account identifier specific to the cloud provider. AwsAccountIdentifier Type The type of the account, eg: AWS/Azure/GCP. String Policy Template This template will give you a quick head start on generating a policy for an AwsAccount:</description></item><item><title>AwsEc2Image</title><link>https://cloudaspect.app/docs/aws/resources/awsec2image/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cloudaspect.app/docs/aws/resources/awsec2image/</guid><description>The AMIs, AKIs, and ARIs available to you or all of the images available to you. The images available to you include public images, private images that you own, and private images owned by other AWS accounts for which you have explicit launch permissions.
Properties Name Description Type Account The account that is associated with the resource. AwsAccount Architecture The architecture of the image.</description></item><item><title>AwsEc2Instance</title><link>https://cloudaspect.app/docs/aws/resources/awsec2instance/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cloudaspect.app/docs/aws/resources/awsec2instance/</guid><description>Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (Amazon EC2) is a web service that provides secure, resizable compute capacity in the cloud. It is designed to make web-scale cloud computing easier for developers. Amazon EC2’s simple web service interface allows you to obtain and configure capacity with minimal friction.
Properties Name Description Type Account The account that is associated with the resource. AwsAccount Architecture The architecture of the image.</description></item><item><title>AwsEc2KeyPair</title><link>https://cloudaspect.app/docs/aws/resources/awsec2keypair/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cloudaspect.app/docs/aws/resources/awsec2keypair/</guid><description>A key pair, consisting of a private key and a public key, is a set of security credentials that you use to prove your identity when connecting to an EC2 instance.
Properties Name Description Type Account The account that is associated with the resource. AwsAccount Arn The Amazon Resource Names (ARN) uniquely identifying an AWS resource. String Fingerprint If you used CreateKeyPair to create the key pair, this is the SHA-1 digest of the DER encoded private key.</description></item><item><title>AwsEc2Snapshot</title><link>https://cloudaspect.app/docs/aws/resources/awsec2snapshot/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cloudaspect.app/docs/aws/resources/awsec2snapshot/</guid><description>Amazon EBS provides the ability to create snapshots (backups) of any EBS volume. A snapshot takes a copy of the EBS volume and places it in Amazon S3, where it is stored redundantly in multiple Availability Zones.
Properties Name Description Type Account The account that is associated with the resource. AwsAccount Arn The Amazon Resource Names (ARN) uniquely identifying an AWS resource.</description></item><item><title>AwsEc2Volume</title><link>https://cloudaspect.app/docs/aws/resources/awsec2volume/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cloudaspect.app/docs/aws/resources/awsec2volume/</guid><description>An Amazon EBS volume is a durable, block-level storage device that you can attach to your instances. After you attach a volume to an instance, you can use it as you would use a physical hard drive.
Properties Name Description Type Account The account that is associated with the resource. AwsAccount Arn The Amazon Resource Names (ARN) uniquely identifying an AWS resource.</description></item><item><title>AwsElasticIp</title><link>https://cloudaspect.app/docs/aws/resources/awselasticip/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cloudaspect.app/docs/aws/resources/awselasticip/</guid><description>An Elastic IP address is a static IPv4 address designed for dynamic cloud computing. you can mask the failure of an instance or software by rapidly remapping the address to another instance in your account. Alternatively, you can specify the Elastic IP address in a DNS record for your domain, so that your domain points to your instance.
Properties Name Description Type Account The account that is associated with the resource.</description></item><item><title>AwsInternetGateway</title><link>https://cloudaspect.app/docs/aws/resources/awsinternetgateway/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cloudaspect.app/docs/aws/resources/awsinternetgateway/</guid><description>Internet gateway are horizontally scaled, redundant, and highly available VPC components that allows communication between your VPC and the internet.
Properties Name Description Type Account The account that is associated with the resource. AwsAccount Arn The Amazon Resource Names (ARN) uniquely identifying an AWS resource. String Attachments Any VPCs attached to the internet gateway. There may be 0 or more entries in this collection.</description></item><item><title>AwsNatGateway</title><link>https://cloudaspect.app/docs/aws/resources/awsnatgateway/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cloudaspect.app/docs/aws/resources/awsnatgateway/</guid><description>Network address translation (NAT) gateways enable instances in a private subnet to connect to the internet or other AWS services, but prevent the internet from initiating a connection with those instances.
Properties Name Description Type Account The account that is associated with the resource. AwsAccount Addresses Information about the IP addresses and network interface associated with the NAT gateway. There may be 0 or more entries in this collection.</description></item><item><title>AwsNetworkInterface</title><link>https://cloudaspect.app/docs/aws/resources/awsnetworkinterface/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cloudaspect.app/docs/aws/resources/awsnetworkinterface/</guid><description>An elastic network interface is a logical networking component in a VPC that represents a virtual network card.
Properties Name Description Type Account The account that is associated with the resource. AwsAccount Arn The Amazon Resource Names (ARN) uniquely identifying an AWS resource. String Association The association information for an Elastic IP address (IPv4) associated with the network interface. NetworkAssociation Attachment The network interface attachment.</description></item><item><title>AwsPrefixList</title><link>https://cloudaspect.app/docs/aws/resources/awsprefixlist/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cloudaspect.app/docs/aws/resources/awsprefixlist/</guid><description>A prefix list is a set of one or more CIDR blocks. You can use prefix lists to make it easier to configure and maintain your security groups and route tables.
Properties Name Description Type Account The account that is associated with the resource. AwsAccount AddressFamily The IP address version. String Arn The Amazon Resource Names (ARN) uniquely identifying an AWS resource.</description></item><item><title>AwsReservedInstance</title><link>https://cloudaspect.app/docs/aws/resources/awsreservedinstance/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cloudaspect.app/docs/aws/resources/awsreservedinstance/</guid><description>Reserved Instances (RI) provide a significant discount (up to 72%) compared to On-Demand pricing for EC2 Instances and provide a capacity reservation when used in a specific Availability Zone.
Properties Name Description Type Account The account that is associated with the resource. AwsAccount Arn The Amazon Resource Names (ARN) uniquely identifying an AWS resource. String AvailabilityZone The Availability Zone in which the Reserved Instance can be used.</description></item><item><title>AwsRouteTable</title><link>https://cloudaspect.app/docs/aws/resources/awsroutetable/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cloudaspect.app/docs/aws/resources/awsroutetable/</guid><description>A route table contains a set of rules, called routes, that are used to determine where network traffic from your subnet or gateway is directed.
Properties Name Description Type Account The account that is associated with the resource. AwsAccount Arn The Amazon Resource Names (ARN) uniquely identifying an AWS resource. String Associations The associations between the route table and one or more subnets or a gateway.</description></item><item><title>AwsSecurityGroup</title><link>https://cloudaspect.app/docs/aws/resources/awssecuritygroup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cloudaspect.app/docs/aws/resources/awssecuritygroup/</guid><description>A security group acts as a virtual firewall for your instance to control inbound and outbound traffic. A security group specifies the actions that are allowed, not the actions that are blocked.
Properties Name Description Type Account The account that is associated with the resource. AwsAccount Arn The Amazon Resource Names (ARN) uniquely identifying an AWS resource. String Description A friendly description of what the security group allows.</description></item><item><title>AwsTransitGateway</title><link>https://cloudaspect.app/docs/aws/resources/awstransitgateway/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cloudaspect.app/docs/aws/resources/awstransitgateway/</guid><description>AWS Transit Gateway connects VPCs and on-premises networks through a central hub. This simplifies your network and puts an end to complex peering relationships. It acts as a cloud router – each new connection is only made once.
Properties Name Description Type Account The account that is associated with the resource. AwsAccount Arn The Amazon Resource Names (ARN) uniquely identifying an AWS resource.</description></item><item><title>AwsVpc</title><link>https://cloudaspect.app/docs/aws/resources/awsvpc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cloudaspect.app/docs/aws/resources/awsvpc/</guid><description>Amazon Virtual Private Cloud (Amazon VPC) is a service that lets you launch AWS resources in a logically isolated virtual network that you define. You have complete control over your virtual networking environment, including selection of your own IP address range, creation of subnets, and configuration of route tables and network gateways. You can use both IPv4 and IPv6 for most resources in your virtual private cloud, helping to ensure secure and easy access to resources and applications.</description></item></channel></rss>