<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Contributing on Aspect</title><link>https://cloudaspect.app/docs/contributing/</link><description>Recent content in Contributing on Aspect</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://cloudaspect.app/docs/contributing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Developing Locally</title><link>https://cloudaspect.app/docs/contributing/local-development/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cloudaspect.app/docs/contributing/local-development/</guid><description>If you wish to modify an aspect of Aspect, you&amp;rsquo;ll need the source code. Clone via one of the following methods:
Clone using SSH git clone --recurse-submodules git@github.com:Im5tu/aspect.git Clone using Github CLI gh repo clone Im5tu/aspect Clone using HTTPS git clone --recurse-submodules https://github.com/Im5tu/aspect.git Building &amp;amp; Running tests In order to build a development build, execute the following command:
dotnet build In order to run the unit tests, execute:
dotnet test The solution is designed to take care of any dependencies that are required so that contributors have the best experience in their local development environments.</description></item><item><title>Code of Conduct</title><link>https://cloudaspect.app/docs/contributing/code-of-conduct/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cloudaspect.app/docs/contributing/code-of-conduct/</guid><description>Our Pledge We as members, contributors, and leaders pledge to make participation in our community a harassment-free experience for everyone, regardless of age, body size, visible or invisible disability, ethnicity, sex characteristics, gender identity and expression, level of experience, education, socio-economic status, nationality, personal appearance, race, caste, color, religion, or sexual identity and orientation.
We pledge to act and interact in ways that contribute to an open, welcoming, diverse, inclusive, and healthy community.</description></item></channel></rss>